What would you like to order?
Today you'll learn 8 phrases to order food in Thai like a local.
When I first moved to Bangkok, there was this noodle stall near my apartment. Every morning, the same aunty would shout at me — สั่งอะไรดีคะ — and I had no idea what to say. I just pointed at the picture.
By the end of this video, you won't need to point. You'll order in Thai, ask for recommendations, tell them how spicy you want it, and get the bill — all in Thai.
to order
What would you like to order?
spicy
not spicy
No spicy, please.
delicious
Very delicious!
may I have / I'd like
I'd like one Pad Thai, please.
check please / bill please
Can I have the bill, please?
to recommend
What do you recommend?
full (not hungry)
I'm full.
What do you recommend?
I'd like one Pad Thai, please.
No spicy, please.
Very delicious!
Can I have the bill, please?
How would you say: 'I'd like one Pad Thai, please'?
Try saying it now...
I'd like one Pad Thai, please.
How would you say: 'No spicy, please'?
Try saying it now...
No spicy, please.
How would you say: 'Can I have the bill, please'?
Try saying it now...
Can I have the bill, please?
Quick recap — here are your 8 phrases for ordering food in Thai.
Next time — asking for directions. You'll learn how to say 'where is...?' and understand the answer.
Where is...?